<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrew van Rooyen</title>
    <description>Software Developer — Cape Town — South Africa</description>
    <link>http://wraithy.github.io//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://wraithy.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:15:03 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:15:03 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Notes to myself</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have never been the kind of person who actively posts on social media. In
fact, if you were to look through my Facebook/Twitter timelines right now, you
would find a bursting collection of “not much”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just &lt;em&gt;who I am&lt;/em&gt;. I have always preferred to consume writing rather than
generate it. I spend a healthy amount of time reading books, and an unhealthy
amount of time sifting through Hacker News and Reddit. So, starting a “blog” is
certainly unusual for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;then-why&quot;&gt;Then why?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I’ve found myself thinking about something specific, and wanting to
record it somewhere. Not for other people to read, but rather to help get my
thoughts in order and maintain an archive, in case I need to come back to that
train of thought in the future. At first I looked into note-taking tools like
Evernote, but ended up leaning towards keeping my own set of markdown files,
which in turn led me here. I see this as an opportunity for me to organize my
thoughts, and take stock of lessons I’ve learned in an open way. If people read
what I post - great. If they don’t - at least I will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have a particular plan for what I’ll be writing, but it will likely
involve&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programming environments&lt;/strong&gt; - Mostly Vim, but also general workflows
inside a terminal&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tooling around programming for the cloud&lt;/strong&gt; - Specifically CI/CD, Docker and
Google Cloud Platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be code snippets. There will be diagrams. There will be opinions.
For now though, I’m just trying to figure out how to work with Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://wraithy.github.io//2016/notes-to-myself/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wraithy.github.io//2016/notes-to-myself/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
